I've realized is, I don't think it's
fair to ask your nearest and dearest
to read the stuff that you've written.
I just don't. And part of the reason
is because of that tenth of an ass
thing,
right? If you're asking people to read
stuff that you've written, they're
used
to reading Finnish stuff.
They don't have, they don't have any
kind of handle on reading stuff that's
not finished. And so I think one of
the things
that you can do, one of the most
helpful things you can do, is to find
somebody,
probably somebody who's somewhere on
the same journey as you trying to
write,
that's prepared to read what you've
written.
And again, don't throw an entire novel
at them.
Like, you know, as I said, we're doing
like two hours a week.
That's tops.